Hans Tanawi

FRONT-END ENGINEER



CONTACT

- **♀** Taipei, Taiwan
- @ hanstanawi@gmail.com
- +886-987-073-094
- github.com/hanstanawi

SKILLS

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, SQL, MongoDB

Frameworks & Libraries

React, Vue, Redux, Vuex, TailiwindCSS, Next.js, Express.js

Tools & Platforms

Docker, Git, Visual Studio Code, Figma, Linux, Firebase

EDUCATION

Bachelor of EngineeringComputer Science

Tunghai University 2017-2021

♥ Taichung,Taiwan

GPA: 3.8

Chinese PreparatoryProgram

NTNU

2015-2017

♥ New Taipei City, Taiwan

PROFILE

Hans Tanawi is a front-end software engineer, who is specializing in building exceptional digital experiences for web applications and fluent in English and Chinese. He graduated from private university in Taichung City, Taiwan in 2021, with Bachelor of Engineering degree from Computer Science department, focusing on Digital Innovative field.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCES

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

LUMINA

♥ Taipei, Taiwan

Lumina is a software and hardware technology company that builds beautifully integrated hardware to make remote work better.

- Lead, develop, and maintain Lumina Next.js landing page development, such as implement AB tests, analytics, and website performance.
- Implement and maintain backend Lambda functions and webhooks using TypeScript.
- Lead, develop, and maintain Lumina REST API using Node.js, NestJS, and PostgreSQL as backend API for Lumina Studio native application.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

MAY 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

MOLTEO

♥ Schleswig, Germany - Remote

Molteo is a digital workspace, which provides real-time overview of projects and construction sites, flexible resource capturing, and paperless billing.

- Write and maintain modern, performant, and robust code of Molteo Vue.js web application.
- Implement thorough web application end-to-end tests using Cypress
- Collaborate with and assist the back-end team developing and maintaining APIs using Express/Feather.js and PostgreSQL
- Assist the migration of the whole front-end codebase from JavaScript to TypeScript

LANGUAGES

- Chinese Professional Working
- English Full Professional

Indonesian - Native